VICTOR VADMAND JENSEN

Borgmestervænget 8, st. th., 9000 Aalborg, Denmark

Date of birth: 13th of November, 1998

+45 61 28 27 33 \diamond villerdk@live.com \diamond LinkedIn \diamond ORCID \diamond GitHub



ABOUT ME

I am an MSc of IT student living in Aalborg, and I am curious about the opportunities which digital technologies provide us, as well as how we can develop these in creative and responsible ways. My educational background gives me the abilities to work with digital technologies in a flexible and user-friendly way, both in design, development, and implementation. Thus, I can participate in the entire process of software development with the users at the core. Throughout my work, I have used this in relation to Aalborg University's research data, smartphone apps in healthcare, as well as IT systems for energy managemement in citizen energy communities.

EDUCATION

IT Design and Application Development, MSc. - Aalborg University

2021 - Present

Master's thesis: "Exploring Hybrid Digital Boardgames as Multi-Player Design Fiction Probes into Energy Communities", which investigates the role algorithms in future energy communities to provide directions for responsible technology development. Development of a partly digital, partly physical design fiction probe, as well as evaluation of this.

Techno-Anthropology, BSc - Aalborg University

2017 - 2021

Bachelor's thesis: "Life in the grey area: digital marginalisation of elderly citizens in the Covid-19 vaccination invitation" about elderly citizens' interaction with IT in regards to Covid-19 vaccination summons using interviews and co-design activities.

SKILLS AND INTERESTS

Skills Ethnographic fieldwork and interviews, user involvement, health technology assessment,

ethical technology assessment, object oriented programming in Python and Java,

usability evaluation, descriptive statistics, project planning.

Interests Human-computer interaction, user-centered design, usability, innovation,

eHealth and mHealth, ethics in technology development, mixed methods research.

EXPERIENCE

Centre on Sustainable and Digital Transformation, Aalborg University

January 2023 – Present

Student assistant

- · Designed an educational game to support interdisciplinary cooperation on sustainability in connection with a research project.
- · Planned and facilitated tests and evaluations of the game with qualitative data collection to iterate on the game.
- · Analyzed 12 digital platforms for game development to plan out and execute the development of a digital version of a learning game.

Human-Centered Computing, Aalborg University

 $May\ 2022-December\ 2022$

Student programmer

- · Executed user interviews and a workshop concerning Energifællesskab Avedøre to create user-centered insights on technology as part of the research project Sektorkobling via Energifællesskaber.
- · Participated in UX design, prototyping, and evaluation of an information display for students at Hvidovre Gymnasium, as well as performed a usability evaluation of a digital platform to identify 35 usability problems.
- · Conducted qualitative data analysis and design of information display as part of a Value-Sensitive Design study for ethical technology development.
- · Lead authored the case study paper "Exploring Values of Energy Justice: A Case Study of a Burgeoning Energy Community", accepted for presentation at CHI 2023.

MedCom May 2022 – July 2022

Freelance, research

· Designed a study and developed a digital questionnaire about citizens' expectations of the project "Apps på recept", regarding prescription of smartphone apps by general practitioners.

- · Analyzed statistical data from a validated questionnaire with 67 responses for tendencies and internal consistency, as well as developed three user personas based on these tendencies.
- · Wrote a report with recommendations for the "Apps på recept" project and participated in a steering group meeting to present findings.

The VBN-team, Aalborg University Library

November 2019 – April 2022

- Student assistant
- · Managed data integrity and data quality of AAU press clippings in Pure, as well as developed and implementated a qualitative categorization procedure for the contents of over 2400 press clippings.
- · Developed and implemented a procedure for the registration of research impact in Pure, as well as contacted researchers about more than 30 cases of research impact.

PEER REVIEWED RESEARCH OUTPUT

Jensen, V. V., & Jensen, R. H. (2023, April). Exploring Values of Energy Justice: A Case Study of a Burgeoning Energy Community. In *Extended Abstracts of the 2023 CHI Conference on Human Factors in Computing Systems* (CHI EA '23) https://doi.org/10.1145/3544549.3573864. 9 pages. First author. Accepted for presentation and publication.

Jensen, V. V., Sørensen, T. H., Kristensen, A. Ø & Eriksen, J. (2023, May). Danish Citizens' Expectations for mHealth Prescription. First author. In 33rd Medical Informatics Europe Conference, MIE 2023. IOS Press. 2 pages. First author. Accepted for presentation and publication.

Jensen, V. V., Pedersen T. & Kloppenborg, S.S. (2022, November 28-29). The Role of Relatives in E-governance Access Among Elderly Citizens: Vignettes from the Danish Covid-19 Vaccination [Paper presentation, based on peer-reviewed abstract]. Welfare After Digitalization, Copenhagen, Denmark. https://vbn.aau.dk/en/activities/the-role-of-relatives-in-e-governance-access-among-elderly-citize. Co-first author and co-presenter.

Christensen, E., Christiansen, I., Pham, K., **Jensen, V. V.**, Persson, J. S. & Hansen, N. B. (TBD). Digitally Mediating Electricity Prices for Consumers and Providers: Action Design Research in an Energy Crisis. Co-first author. In preparation for *Scandinavian Journal of Information Systems*.

RESEARCH DISSEMINATION

Hansen, R. M., Kloppenborg, S. S., Pedersen, T. & **Jensen**, **V. V.**. (2021). *Life in the grey area: Digital marginalisation of elderly citizens in the Covid-19 vaccination invitation*, Bachelor thesis; BA; Techno-Anthropology; Aalborg University. Danish Association for Science and Technology Studies. https://www.dasts.dk/?page_id=4446. 100 pages. Co-first author.

Jensen, V. V., Jensen, R. H., Laursen, K., & Kjærup, M. (2023). Sektorkobling via Energifællesskaber: Værdi-Sensitivt Design i Energifællesskab Avedøre – Forskningsnotat. Aalborg University. 43 pages. First author.

Pedersen, T., **Jensen, V. V.**, Kloppenborg, S. S. & Hansen, R. M. (TBD). The Role of Relatives in E-governance Access Among Elderly Citizens: Vignettes from the Danish Covid-19 Vaccination. In V. Galis & V.-S. Vlassis (Ed.), Welfare After Digitalization: digitalizing welfare, outsourcing responsibility. Co-first author. Accepted for publication, currently in preparation.